Contact

ss9334931@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sahibpreetsingh-16572b171 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel
Microsoft PowerPoint

Honors-Awards

Udacity Bertelsmann Scholar

Top 0.2 percent(Kaggle kernels) of
Kagglers Globally

2nd Rank In Data science Hackathon by IEEE

Kaggle Kernels Master

3x Kaggle Expert

Sahibpreet singh

3 x Kaggle Expert , Udacity Bertelsmann Scholar, Data-Scientist Patiala

Summary

I am a Data Science enthusiast and Python Developer and I have been working with python for the last 3 years. I have worked in several projects related to Computer vision, NLP and Data Analysis. I have secured Rank in top 200 from over 1 million people on Kaggle (kernels).

I have been worked with my professor on a project that is aimed to help hearing impaired People.

and Last I beleive life stops as learning ends.

Experience

Tatras Data
Jr. Data Scientist
July 2020 - Present (2 months)

Sabudh Foundation
Data Science Intern
January 2020 - June 2020 (6 months)
Mohali

Eduwaive Foundation

Intern

August 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Patiala, Punjab

I am a Tech Enthusiast. Interested in Automation and Text Analysis currently working as Python Developer. In the last 2 years, I have worked in 2 projects as a freelancer which involved Web Scrapping and Website development using Flask.

My greatest strength is to make people comfortable while working in a team Project

Education

Punjabi University
Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering, Data
Processing · (2016 - 2020)

Sri Aurobindo International School,Patiala High School , Non-Medical

University college of engineering, Punjabi Univerity Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering